<journey name="Load descriptor via QR scan">
    <description>
        Opens the descriptor QR scanner from Settings, falls back to the paste path (the
        scanner sheet is a bottom sheet, and an emulator/device may not have a usable
        camera), submits a wallet descriptor, confirms it in the confirmation dialog, and
        verifies the descriptor list updates without the app crashing.

        Camera-dependent steps are SKIPPABLE when the device has no camera. The paste
        fallback inside the sheet and the confirmation dialog are rendered in separate
        windows, so their controls are targeted by visible text, not testTag.
    </description>
    <actions>
        <action>Launch the Mandacaru app and wait for the splash screen to dismiss (poll until nav_node is present)</action>
        <action>Tap the Settings navigation item (nav_settings)</action>
        <action>Expand the Descriptors section if it is collapsed</action>
        <action>Tap the Scan QR button (button_scan_descriptor)</action>
        <action>Verify the descriptor scan sheet opens — either a camera preview or, if camera permission is denied/unavailable, a "Camera permission is required" fallback (SKIPPABLE: depends on device camera)</action>
        <action>Tap the "Paste instead" button (target by text) to switch the sheet to paste mode</action>
        <action>Tap the paste text field and type "wpkh([73c5da0a/84h/1h/0h]tpubDC8msFGeGuwnKG9Upg7DM2b4DaRqg3CUZa5g8v2SRQ6K4NSkxUgd7HsL2XVWbVm39yBA4LgAFKvDsdsBPzMw3RGYbjeMs9dGcTLeUw6f7c/0/*)"</action>
        <action>Tap the "Decode" button (target by text) to submit the pasted descriptor</action>
        <action>Verify a confirmation dialog appears showing the decoded descriptor and a detected script type (e.g. "Native SegWit") (target by text)</action>
        <action>Tap the "Load" button in the confirmation dialog (target by text)</action>
        <action>Verify the descriptors list shows the loaded descriptor or a confirmation snackbar, and the app has not crashed</action>
    </actions>
</journey>
