<journey name="Share descriptor as Electrum key">
    <description>
        Loads a native-SegWit descriptor, opens the share sheet from the descriptor row, and
        verifies both tabs: the default Descriptor tab shows the full descriptor, and the
        Extended-key tab shows the SLIP-132 zpub Electrum expects (issue #121). The sheet is a
        ModalBottomSheet, so its tabs and buttons are targeted by visible text, not testTags.
    </description>
    <actions>
        <action>Launch the Mandacaru app and wait for the splash screen to dismiss (poll until nav_node is present)</action>
        <action>Tap the Settings navigation item (nav_settings)</action>
        <action>Expand the Descriptors section if it is collapsed</action>
        <action>Tap the descriptor field (input_descriptor)</action>
        <action>Type "wpkh([73c5da0a/84h/0h/0h]xpub6CFy3kRXorC3NMTt8qrsY9ucUfxVLXyFQ49JSLm3iEG5gfAmWewYFzjNYFgRiCjoB9WWEuJQiyYGCdZvUTwPEUPL9pPabT8bkbiD9Po47XG/0/*)" into the descriptor field (input_descriptor)</action>
        <action>Tap the Update descriptor button (button_update_descriptor)</action>
        <action>Verify the descriptors list shows the loaded descriptor and the app has not crashed</action>
        <action>Tap the loaded descriptor row (button_share_descriptor; if more than one row is present, target the first) to open the share sheet</action>
        <action>Verify the share sheet is open showing two tabs, "Descriptor" and "Extended key" (target by text), with the Descriptor tab selected by default and a QR code visible</action>
        <action>Verify the "Modern wallets like Sparrow, BlueWallet, Specter" description is shown under the Descriptor tab (target by text)</action>
        <action>Tap the "Extended key" tab (target by text)</action>
        <action>Verify the Extended-key tab shows a zpub key beginning with "zpub" (target by text), a QR code, and the "Electrum and older wallets" description</action>
        <action>Tap the Copy button on the Extended-key tab (target by the "Copy" text)</action>
        <action>Verify an "Extended public key copied to clipboard" snackbar appears (target by text) and the app has not crashed</action>
    </actions>
</journey>
